Ijeoma Onuaju

Frontend Developer

Contact Lagos, Nigeria +234 803 277 9222

ijeomaonuajurx@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ijeomaonuaju

Profile

https://her-excellency.netlify.app/

Technical Skills

HTML CSS/Bootstrap React JS JavaScript PHP MVC SQL

Version Control

Git Github

Soft Skills

Communication
Team spirit
Creativity
Leadership
Interpersonal skills
Work ethic
Attention to detail

Profile

A positive experienced web developer who can work both alone and as part of a team. I have technical capabilities and ability to ensure all work is optimized across a wide range of platforms. A readiness to embrace and use new approaches and to keep up-to-date with industry advances

Experience

August 2020—Present
Frontend Developer • Agrorite• Lagos, Nigeria

An Agri-tech company with a farm management and funds management app. Built the website and Agrorite bookies web app (frontend).

Translated UI designs into beautiful responsive and fluid layouts. Supervised the team's activities. Ability to output clean, commented and team-friendly code. Built out reusable components. Ensured mobile responsiveness. Reviewed and merged Pull Requests raised by team members. Optimized performance to ensure fast loading websites. Pitched the web app (bookies) to clients.

February 2020 — November 2021 Frontend Developer• Reaprite Global, Itd• Lagos, Nigeria A fintech company with various savings options

Built company's website. Replicated UI designs to meet product requirements. Wrote reusable and modular code using PHP, JavaScript and Bootstrap. Made website Responsive across all devices. Demonstrated good interpersonal and communication skills. Participated in planning sessions and project retrospectives

September 2020—present Frontend Developer• Foodies.NG• Lagos, Nigeria An online food store.

Ensure website functionality and perform software updates. Monitor, assess, and report on website performance. Develop and/or update content. Make adjustments to the design

Education

Nov. 2022 Software Engineering • in-view ALX

Dec. 2014

B.Sc.• Microbiology• Nigeria

Federal University of Agriculture, Abeokuta